Library. University Librarian. Administrative files UARC.0377
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 7.559 - Custodial services., 1974-1975.; 892952 (Box 236, Folder 9)
- 7.565 - Police Department., 1973-1976.; 892951 (Box 236, Folder 10)
- 7.570 - Political Science, Department of., 1974-1976.; 892950 (Box 236, Folder 11)
- 7.575 - Printing and production., 1976.; 892949 (Box 236, Folder 12)
- 7.585 - Public Affairs - Public Information Office., 1975.; 892948 (Box 236, Folder 13)
- 7.591 - Public lectures., 1974-1976.; 892947 (Box 236, Folder 14)
- 7.595 - Purchasing, Department of., 1974-1976.; 892946 (Box 236, Folder 15)
- 7.610 - Records Management Program., 1974-1976.; 892945 (Box 236, Folder 16)
- 7.630 - Russian and East European Studies Center., 1974-1976.; 892944 (Box 236, Folder 17)
- 7.650 - Speech Department., 1974.; 892943 (Box 236, Folder 18)
- 7.674 - Student I.D. Card., 1976.; 892942 (Box 236, Folder 19)
- 7.680 - Telecommunications Center., 1974-1976.; 892941 (Box 236, Folder 20)
- 7.690 - Theater Arts, Department of., 1974.; 892940 (Box 236, Folder 21)
- 7.705 - Urban Center., 1971.; 892939 (Box 236, Folder 22)
- 8.005 - American Association of University Professors., 1969-1973.; 892938 (Box 236, Folder 23)
- 8.020 - American Library Association., 1971-1976.; 892937 (Box 236, Folder 24)
- 8.021 - ALA shelflist measurement., 1973-1975.; 892936 (Box 236, Folder 25)
- 8.025 - Association of College and Research Libraries., 892935 (Box 236, Folder 26)
- 8.030 - Association of Research Libraries., 1966-1976.; 892934 (Box 237, Folder 1)
- 8.032 - ARL - InterLibrary Loan Study., 1971-1972.; 892933 (Box 237, Folder 2)
- 8.033 - ARL - InterLibrary Communication - SILC-Hayes Report., 1972-1973.; 892932 (Box 237, Folder 3)
- 8.045 - California Librarian., 1970-1975.; 892931 (Box 237, Folder 4)
- 8.050 - California Library Association., 1972-1976.; 892930 (Box 237, Folder 5)
- 8.053 - Council for Computerized Library Networks., 1975.; 892929 (Box 237, Folder 6)
- 8.055 - Council on Library Resources., 1970-1976.; 892928 (Box 237, Folder 7)
- 8.057 - CLR - Library Management Intern Program., 1974-1976.; 892927 (Box 238, Folder 1)
- 8.060 - Center for Research Libraries., 1971-1976.; 892926 (Box 238, Folder 2-3)
- 8.089 - Infor., 1970-1973.; 892925 (Box 238, Folder 4)
- 8.110 - KTO Limited., 1972.; 892924 (Box 238, Folder 5)
- 8.125 - Library Journal., 1969-1974.; 892923 (Box 238, Folder 6)
- 8.135 - Manuscript Society., 1972.; 892922 (Box 238, Folder 7)
- 8.137 - Medieval Academy of America., 1971-1973.; 892921 (Box 238, Folder 8)
- 8.140 - Modern Language Association., 1970.; 892920 (Box 239, Folder 1)
- 8.142 - Music Library Association., 1973.; 892919 (Box 239, Folder 2)
- 8.150 - National Commission on Library and Information Science., 1971-1976.; 892918 (Box 239, Folder 3)
- 8.160 - Oral History Association., 1973.; 892917 (Box 239, Folder 4)
- 8.186 - Rare Book Libraries Conference., 1971-1973.; 892916 (Box 239, Folder 5)
- 8.200 - Technical Service Directors of Large Research Libraries., 1963-1975.; 892915 (Box 239, Folder 6)
- 8.230 - Western Association of Schools and Colleges., 1967-1972.; 892914 (Box 239, Folder 7)
- 8.235 - Wilson Library Bulletin., 1970-1973.; 892913 (Box 239, Folder 8)
- 8.300 - U.C. Librarian., 1976.; 892912 (Box 239, Folder 9)
- 9.005 - A - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892911 (Box 239, Folder 10)
- 9.006 - Abel proposal., 1973-1975.; 892910 (Box 239, Folder 11)
- 9.035 - B - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892909 (Box 239, Folder 12)
- 9.040 - Baker, Robert Stanley., 1976.; 892908 (Box 239, Folder 13)
- 9.050 - Fletcher Bowron Project., 1963-1968.; 892907 (Box 239, Folder 14)
  General
  Found loose in the stacks 1981 Feb 12.
- 9.060 - C - miscellaneous., 1973-1976.; 892906 (Box 239, Folder 15)
- 9.100 - D - miscellaneous., 1974.; 892905 (Box 239, Folder 16)
- 9.115 - E - miscellaneous., 1974.; 892904 (Box 239, Folder 17)
- 9.125 - F - miscellaneous., 1974-1975.; 892903 (Box 239, Folder 18)
- 9.130 - Fritz, Mrs. Bernard., 1974-1975.; 892902 (Box 239, Folder 19)
- 9.140 - G - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892901 (Box 239, Folder 20)
- 9.165 - H - miscellaneous., 1971-1976.; 892900 (Box 239, Folder 21)
- 9.195 - IBM., 1975.; 892899 (Box 239, Folder 22)
- 9.200 - J - miscellaneous., 1972-1974.; 892898 (Box 239, Folder 23)
- 9.210 - K - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892897 (Box 239, Folder 24)
- 9.235 - L - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892896 (Box 239, Folder 25)
- 9.240 - L.A. Times., 1975.; 892895 (Box 239, Folder 26)
- 9.245 - M - miscellaneous., 1973-1975.; 892894 (Box 240, Folder 1)
- 9.270 - Murphy, Franklin D. Associates., 1975-1976.; 892893 (Box 240, Folder 2)
- 9.280 - N - miscellaneous., 1971-1974.; 892892 (Box 240, Folder 3)
- 9.305 - O - miscellaneous., 1975.; 892891 (Box 240, Folder 4)
- 9.310 - P - miscellaneous., 1974-1980.; 892890 (Box 240, Folder 5)
- 9.320 - Powell, Lawrence Clark., 1974-1976.; 892889 (Box 240, Folder 6)
- 9.330 - R - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892888 (Box 240, Folder 7)
- 9.355 - S - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892887 (Box 240, Folder 8)
- 9.380 - Stevens and Brown, B. F., 1974-1975.; 892886 (Box 240, Folder 9)
- 9.400 - T - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892885 (Box 240, Folder 10)
- 9.415 - U - miscellaneous., 1974-1975.; 892884 (Box 240, Folder 11)
- 9.430 - University microfilm., 1974-1975.; 892883 (Box 240, Folder 12)
- 9.435 - V - miscellaneous., 1976.; 892882 (Box 240, Folder 13)
- 9.440 - W - miscellaneous., 1974-1976.; 892881 (Box 240, Folder 14)
- 9.460 - Wilson Co., H.W., 1974-1976.; 892880 (Box 240, Folder 15)
- 9.470 - X - miscellaneous., 1974.; 892879 (Box 240, Folder 16)
- 9.485 - Zeitlin, Mr. Jacob., 1974.; 892878 (Box 240, Folder 17)
- 10.005 - Budget - campus., 1965-1975.; 892877 (Box 240, Folder 18)
- 10.010 - Budget and accounting., 1970-1972.; 892876 (Box 240, Folder 19)
- 10.030 - miscellaneous budget., 1965-1975.; 892875 (Box 240, Folder 20)
- 10.035 - Special funding., 1966-1976.; 892874 (Box 240, Folder 21)
- 10.038 - Accounting., 1975.; 892873 (Box 240, Folder 22)
- 10.040 - Budget - Library., 1971-1976.; 892872 (Box 240, Folder 23)
- 10.045 - Book budget., 1970-1976.; 892871 (Box 241, Folder 1)
- 10.046 - Connell Fund., 1966-1971.; 892870 (Box 241, Folder 2)
- 10.048 - Emergency measures., 1970-1971.; 892869 (Box 241, Folder 3)
- 10.050 - Emergency measures (Regents)., 1967-1973.; 892868 (Box 241, Folder 4)
- 10.055 - Equipment and furniture., 1965-1974.; 892867 (Box 241, Folder 5)
- 10.060 - Miscellaneous., 1968-1976.; 892866 (Box 241, Folder 6)
- 10.065 - Supplies and expense., 1966-1975.; 892865 (Box 241, Folder 7)
- 10.067 - Travel., 1969-1976.; 892864 (Box 241, Folder 8)
- 10.068 - Contracts and grants., 1972-1976.; 892863 (Box 241, Folder 9)
- 10.070 - Applications pending., 1970-1973.; 892862 (Box 241, Folder 10)
- 10.085 - Ford Foundation., 1963-1974.; 892861 (Box 242, Folder 1)
- 10.100 - Higher Education Act., 1965-1972.; 892860 (Box 242, Folder 2)
- 10.101 - Office of Education College Library Resource Program., 1973-1975.; 892859 (Box 242, Folder 3)
- 10.101 - Office of Education College Library Resource Grant., 1970-1971/1972.; 892858 (Box 242, Folder 4)
- 10.110 - Medlars., 1966-1974.; 892857 (Box 242, Folder 5)
- 10.114 - National Endowment for the Arts., 1973-1976.; 892856 (Box 242, Folder 6-7)
- 10.115 - National Endowment for the Humanities., 1966-1976.; 892855 (Box 242, Folder 8)
- 10.118 - National Library of Medicine., 1964-1973.; 892854 (Box 242, Folder 9)
- 10.125 - National Science Foundation., 1962-1975.; 892853 (Box 243, Folder 1)
- 10.130 - Office of Contract and Grant Administration., 1962-1975.; 892852 (Box 243, Folder 2)
- 10.145 - State Tech. SVC account., 1967-1970.; 892851 (Box 243, Folder 3)
- 10.150 - U.S. Office of Education., 1972-1975.; 892850 (Box 243, Folder 4)
- 10.155 - USPHS., 1971.; 892849 (Box 243, Folder 5)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Architecture and Urban Planning., 1974-1977.; 892848 (Box 244, Folder 1)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Art Library., 1973-1977.; 892847 (Box 244, Folder 2)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Audio-Visual Consultant., 1970; 1972-1974.; 892846 (Box 244, Folder 3)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Bibliographers., 1968-1976.; 892845 (Box 244, Folder 4-8)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Biomedical Library., 1969-1971.; 892844 (Box 244, Folder 9-10)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Biomedical Library., 1970-1977.; 892843 (Box 245, Folder 1-3)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Chemistry Library., 1969-1974.; 892842 (Box 245, Folder 4)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Circulation Department., 1973-1974.; 892841 (Box 245, Folder 5)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - College Library., 1970-1973.; 892840 (Box 245, Folder 6-9)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - College Library., 1973-1977.; 892839 (Box 246, Folder 1-4)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - William Clark Memorial Library., 1969-1972.; 892838 (Box 246, Folder 5)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Acquisition., 1972-1977.; 892837 (Box 246, Folder 6)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Computerized Information Services., 1975/1976.; 892836 (Box 246, Folder 7)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Education and Psychology Library., 1969-1977.; 892835 (Box 246, Folder 8-12)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Engineering and Math Sciences Library., 1969-1974.; 892834 (Box 247, Folder 1)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - English Reading Room., 1967-1977.; 892833 (Box 247, Folder 2)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Geology-Geophysics Library., 1969-1975.; 892832 (Box 247, Folder 3)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Graduate School and Management Library., 1968/1969; 1976 Jul-Dec.; 892831 (Box 247, Folder 4)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Graduate School and Management Library reports., 1971-1976.; 892830 (Box 247, Folder 5)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Law Library., 1970-1973.; 892829 (Box 247, Folder 6)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Map Library., 1969-1977.; 892828 (Box 248, Folder 1)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Music Library., 1969-1975.; 892827 (Box 248, Folder 2)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Ohio College Library Center., 1974/1975.; 892826 (Box 248, Folder 3)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Oral History Program., 1973/1974.; 892825 (Box 248, Folder 4)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Physics Library., 1968-1974.; 892824 (Box 249, Folder 1)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Public Affairs Service., 1969-1977.; 892823 (Box 249, Folder 2)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Reference Department., 1969-1977.; 892822 (Box 249, Folder 3)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Serials Department., 1969-1977.; 892821 (Box 249, Folder 4)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Systems Department., 1970-1974.; 892820; 3 folders (Box 250, Folder 1)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Task Force., 1971-1977.; 892819 (Box 251, Folder 1)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Technical Services Department - Acquisitions Department., 1969/1970.; 892818 (Box 251, Folder 2)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Technical Services Department - Catalog Department., 1970 Jan-Mar.; 892817 (Box 251, Folder 3)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Technical Services Department., 1972-1977.; 892816 (Box 251, Folder 4)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - Theater Arts Library., 1970-1977.; 892815 (Box 251, Folder 5)
- Annual reports of Library Units to the University Librarian - University Elementary School Library., 1970-1977.; 892814 (Box 251, Folder 6)
- Engineering - montly reports., 1949/1950.; 892813 (Box 252, Folder 1)
- Geology-Physics - monthly reports., 1949/1950.; 892812 (Box 252, Folder 2)
- Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1949/1950.; 892811 (Box 252, Folder 3)
- Reserve Book Room - monthly reports., 1949/1950.; 892810 (Box 252, Folder 4)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1949/1950.; 892809 (Box 252, Folder 5)
- Acquisitions - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892808 (Box 252, Folder 6)
- Branches - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892807 (Box 252, Folder 7)
- Catalog - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892806 (Box 252, Folder 8)
- Circulation - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892805 (Box 252, Folder 9)
- Clark Library - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892804 (Box 252, Folder 10)
- Reference - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892803 (Box 252, Folder 11)
- Special Collections - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892802 (Box 252, Folder 12)
- University of California Libraries - annual report., 1949/1950.; 892801 (Box 252, Folder 13)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892800 (Box 252, Folder 14)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892799 (Box 252, Folder 15)
- Circulation - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892798 (Box 252, Folder 16)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892797 (Box 252, Folder 17)
- Agriculture Reference Library - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892796 (Box 252, Folder 18)
- Biomedical Library - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892795 (Box 252, Folder 19)
- Chemistry Library - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892794 (Box 252, Folder 20)
- Geology and Physics - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892793 (Box 252, Folder 21)
- Institute of Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892792 (Box 252, Folder 22)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892791 (Box 252, Folder 23)
- Engineering Library - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892790 (Box 252, Folder 24)
- Reserve Book Room - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892789 (Box 253, Folder 1)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1948/1949.; 892788 (Box 253, Folder 2)
- Acquisitions - annual report., 1948/1949.; 892787 (Box 253, Folder 3)
- Branch annual reports., 1948 Jul.; 892786 (Box 253, Folder 4)
- Branches - annual report., 1948/1949.; 892785 (Box 253, Folder 5)
- Catalog - annual report., 1948/1949.; 892784 (Box 253, Folder 6)
- Circulation - annual report., 1948/1949.; 892783 (Box 253, Folder 7)
- Clark Library - annual report., 1948/1949.; 892782 (Box 253, Folder 8)
- Reference - annual report., 1948/1949.; 892781 (Box 253, Folder 9)
- Special Collections - annual report., 1948/1949.; 892780 (Box 253, Folder 10)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892779 (Box 253, Folder 11)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892778 (Box 253, Folder 12)
- Circulation - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892777 (Box 253, Folder 13)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892776 (Box 253, Folder 14)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892775 (Box 253, Folder 15)
- Agriculture Reference Library - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892774 (Box 253, Folder 16)
- Biomedical - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892773 (Box 253, Folder 17)
- Chemistry - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892772 (Box 253, Folder 18)
- Engineering - montly reports., 1947/1948.; 892771 (Box 253, Folder 19)
- Geology-Physics - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892770 (Box 253, Folder 20)
- Institute of Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892769 (Box 253, Folder 21)
- Reserve Book Room - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892768 (Box 253, Folder 22)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1947/1948.; 892767 (Box 253, Folder 23)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1946/1947.; 892766 (Box 254, Folder 1)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1946/1947.; 892765 (Box 254, Folder 2)
- Circulation - monthly reports., 1946/1947.; 892764 (Box 254, Folder 3)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1946/1947.; 892763 (Box 254, Folder 4)
- Engineering - montly reports., 1946/1947.; 892762 (Box 254, Folder 5)
- Institute of Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1946/1947.; 892761 (Box 254, Folder 6)
- Reserve Book Room - monthly reports., 1946/1947.; 892760 (Box 254, Folder 7)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1946/1947.; 892759 (Box 254, Folder 8)
- Argiculture - monthly reports., 1945/1947.; 892758 (Box 254, Folder 9)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1945 Feb-1946 Jun.; 892757 (Box 254, Folder 10)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1944-1946.; 892756 (Box 254, Folder 11)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1944/1946.; 892755 (Box 254, Folder 12)
- Circulation - monthly reports., 1944/1946.; 892754 (Box 254, Folder 13)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1944-1946.; 892753 (Box 254, Folder 14)
- Engineering - monthly reports., 1944/1946.; 892752 (Box 254, Folder 15)
- Institute of Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1944/1946.; 892751 (Box 254, Folder 16)
- Reserve Book Room - monthly reports., 1944/1946.; 892750 (Box 254, Folder 17)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1944/1946.; 892749 (Box 254, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous - monthly reports., 892748 (Box 254, Folder 19)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892747 (Box 255, Folder 1)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892746 (Box 255, Folder 2)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892745 (Box 255, Folder 3)
- Special Collections - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892744 (Box 255, Folder 4)
- Agriculture - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892743 (Box 255, Folder 5)
- Art - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892742 (Box 255, Folder 6)
- Biomedical - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892741 (Box 255, Folder 7)
- Chemistry - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892740 (Box 255, Folder 8)
- Education - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892739 (Box 255, Folder 9)
- Engineering - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892738 (Box 255, Folder 10)
- Home Economics - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892737 (Box 255, Folder 11)
- Music - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892736 (Box 255, Folder 12)
- Physics - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892735 (Box 255, Folder 13)
- Theater Arts - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892734 (Box 255, Folder 14)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892733 (Box 255, Folder 15)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1955/1956.; 892732 (Box 255, Folder 16)
- Acquisitions - Annual reports., 1955/1956.; 892731 (Box 255, Folder 17)
- Catalog - Annual reports., 1955/1956.; 892730 (Box 255, Folder 18)
- Circulation - annual report., 1955/1956.; 892729 (Box 255, Folder 19)
- Reference - annual report., 1955/1956.; 892728 (Box 255, Folder 20)
- Special Collections - annual report., 1955/1956.; 892727 (Box 255, Folder 21)
- Clark Library - annual report., 1955/1956.; 892726 (Box 255, Folder 22)
- Branches - annual report., 1955/1956.; 892725 (Box 255, Folder 23)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892724 (Box 256, Folder 1)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892723 (Box 256, Folder 2)
- Circulation - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892722 (Box 256, Folder 3)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892721 (Box 256, Folder 4)
- Special Collections - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892720 (Box 256, Folder 5)
- Agriculture - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892719 (Box 256, Folder 6)
- Art - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892718 (Box 256, Folder 7)
- Biomedical - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892717 (Box 256, Folder 8)
- Chemistry - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892716 (Box 256, Folder 9)
- Education - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892715 (Box 256, Folder 10)
- Engineering - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892714 (Box 256, Folder 11)
- Geology - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892713 (Box 256, Folder 12)
- Institute of Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892712 (Box 256, Folder 13)
- Physics - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892711 (Box 256, Folder 14)
- Theater Arts - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892710 (Box 256, Folder 15)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892709 (Box 256, Folder 16)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1954/1955.; 892708 (Box 256, Folder 17)
- Acquisitions - annual report., 1954/1955.; 892707 (Box 256, Folder 18)
- Catalog - annual report., 1954/1955.; 892706 (Box 256, Folder 19)
- Circulation - annual report., 1954/1955.; 892705 (Box 256, Folder 20)
- Reference - annual report., 1954/1955.; 892704 (Box 256, Folder 21)
- Special Collections - annual report., 1954/1956.; 892703 (Box 256, Folder 22)
- Branches - annual report., 1954/1955.; 892702 (Box 257, Folder 1)
- Clark Library - annual report., 1954/1955.; 892701 (Box 257, Folder 2)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892700 (Box 257, Folder 3)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892699 (Box 257, Folder 4)
- Circulation - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892698 (Box 257, Folder 5)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892697 (Box 257, Folder 6)
- Special Collections - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892696 (Box 257, Folder 7)
- Agriculture - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892695 (Box 257, Folder 8)
- Art - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892694 (Box 257, Folder 9)
- Biomedical - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892693 (Box 257, Folder 10)
- Chemistry - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892692 (Box 257, Folder 11)
- Education - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892691 (Box 257, Folder 12)
- Engineering - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892690 (Box 257, Folder 13)
- Geology - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892689 (Box 257, Folder 14)
- Institute of Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892688 (Box 257, Folder 15)
- Meteorology - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892687 (Box 257, Folder 16)
- Physics - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892686 (Box 257, Folder 17)
- Theater Arts - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892685 (Box 257, Folder 18)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892684 (Box 257, Folder 19)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1953/1954.; 892683 (Box 257, Folder 20)
- Acquisitions - annual report., 1953/1954.; 892682 (Box 257, Folder 21)
- Catalog - annual report., 1953/1954.; 892681 (Box 257, Folder 22)
- Circulation - annual report., 1953/1954.; 892680 (Box 257, Folder 23)
- Reference - annual report., 1953/1954.; 892679 (Box 257, Folder 24)
- Special Collections - annual report., 1953/1954.; 892678 (Box 258, Folder 1)
- Branches - annual report., 1953/1954.; 892677 (Box 258, Folder 2)
- Clark Library - annual report., 1953/1954.; 892676 (Box 258, Folder 3)
- Acquisitions - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892675 (Box 258, Folder 4)
- Catalog - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892674 (Box 258, Folder 5)
- Circulation - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892673 (Box 258, Folder 6)
- Reference - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892672 (Box 258, Folder 7)
- Special Collections - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892671 (Box 258, Folder 8)
- Argiculture - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892670 (Box 258, Folder 9)
- Art - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892669 (Box 258, Folder 10)
- Biomedical - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892668 (Box 258, Folder 11)
- Chemistry - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892667 (Box 258, Folder 12)
- Engineering - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892666 (Box 258, Folder 13)
- Geology - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892665 (Box 258, Folder 14)
- Industrial Relations - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892664 (Box 258, Folder 15)
- Theater Arts - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892663 (Box 258, Folder 16)
- University Elementary School - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892662 (Box 258, Folder 17)
- Clark Library - monthly reports., 1952/1953.; 892661 (Box 258, Folder 18)